{
    "id": "79485c3c49ba41a59da4bc84421e036b",
    "title": "Had Better",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You had better ..................... the tickets now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "buy",
                "bought",
                "to buy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4405a230aa942cfa56c9fb162827b0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ......................... another car now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to not buy",
                "not to buy",
                "not buy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0f0f0be1a72c4d2c8b4b2a4817a06a80"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ....................... this medicine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to take",
                "take",
                "taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68f834e5969e4312aff30c658682645e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had better ..................... on him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not depend",
                "not to depend",
                "to not depend"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6833edd1b56e480fbceca6929a1f51f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ....................... quarrelling with her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to stop",
                "stop",
                "stopped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9ec25d0f1caa4777b1e29a9a8df4556a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ..................... the door before you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to lock",
                "lock",
                "locked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d84f962109a4487694b81f4d8d910c94"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ...................... in the hostel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "to stay",
                "stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1090d52a47bf48e284c388dc0adb66be"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had better ..................... this book soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "publish",
                "to publish",
                "published"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd822bed5a974b1cb62efc0d0ca6b072"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ....................... him one of these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "to visit",
                "visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c95138c523e141f8aae2ec860f333151"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ..................... your money in some profitable business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invest",
                "to invest",
                "invested"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34ffbce5ba3a492fa902f306b066c32d"
        }
    ]
}